Contact

0565067026 (Mobile) aaalotaibi2@kau.edu.sa

www.linkedin.com/in/amal-ahmad-alotaibi- (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Programming

Java

JavaScript

Languages

Arabic

English

Certifications

Machine learning

Amal Ahmad AlOtaibi

Saudi girl wishes fair life and excellent opportunities for women working in the Information Technology

Summary

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the higher education industry. Skilled in back end programing languages like (Python ,Java,C#, C++,vb.net),front end design with (jQuery,Javascript ,Html ,CSS) , Databases Design (Orcale ,SQL SERVER ,IPM db2) . Strong information technology professional with in progress Master's degree focused in Computer Science from King Abdul Aziz University.

Experience

King AbdulAziz University Software and Web Developer 2011 - Present

King AbdulAziz University
Training Supervisor
May 2017 - October 2017 (6 months)
Saudi Arabia

Training Supervisor Web development track

Techie bits
Training Supervisor
May 2016 - October 2016 (6 months)
Saudi Arabia

Training Supervisor Web development track

King AbdulAziz University
Training Supervisor
May 2014 - October 2014 (6 months)
Saudi Arabia

Training Supervisor Web Develoment track

REMAX Real Estate Group

Programmer

February 2010 - April 2010 (3 months)

I worked as a programmer in the marketing department and real estate valuation company Remax Aziza during summer training

Education

King AbdulAziz University

Master's degree, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

King AbdulAziz University

Bachelor's degree with A grade, Computer Science · (2007 - 2011)